<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addons>
<addon id="plugin.program.daveyclanwizard" name="[COLOR orchid]DaveyClan[/COLOR]" version="1.0.0" provider-name="DaveyClan">
  <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.six" />
        <import addon="script.module.kodi-six" />
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py">
    <provides>executable</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.service" library="startup.py" start="startup" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">DaveyClan is a team of individuals that does what it can to provide others, you the best in entertainment.</summary>
        <description lang="en">Many come, Many go. The true and dedicated are here.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 3, 29 June 2007</license>
        <disclaimer lang="en">The author of this addon do not host any of the content which is found and have no affiliation with any of the content providers. This addon simply searches websites for content. Use at your own risk!</disclaimer>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
    </extension>

</addon>

<addon id="plugin.program.Aethernexus" name="[COLOR purple]Aether Nexus[/COLOR]" version="1.0.0" provider-name="Aether">
  <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py">
    <provides>executable</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">Aether Nexus</summary>
        <description lang="en">Aether Nexus

Aether Nexus is the central hub of the Aether ecosystem — designed to deliver a seamless, guided setup with precision and speed.

Built with simplicity in mind, Nexus gives you instant access to Aether builds, system tools, and essential integrations, all in one refined interface. From first install to full optimisation, every step is streamlined to eliminate clutter and maximise performance.

With intelligent configuration, integrated account linking, and automated maintenance tools, Aether Nexus ensures your setup stays fast, clean, and ready to perform.

No guesswork. No unnecessary steps. Just a smooth, elevated experience — exactly how streaming should be.

Stream Above.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
  </extension>
  
</addon>
  
</addons>
